[sighing]
Victim's the local chief
of police. Marnie Green.
Shot twice in the chest,
once in the head.
Trucker found the body,
called it in just after 5:00.
First responder was a, uh,
officer from her department.
Where is he?
Just over here.
Clarence Price.
Agent Lisbon with the CBI.
My condolences.
Any idea what the chief was
doing out here last night?
No, ma'am.
Weren't any calls on the radio.
'Does she have family
around here?'
Chief lived alone.
Worked pretty much 24/7.
[voice breaking]
Truly a good-hearted person.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- We can do this later.
- No, I'm fine, really.
Were there any casings?
Uh, one, from a .380.
One? But she was
shot three times.
Got people looking
for the others.
Alright.
[police radio chatter]
[Wayne]
What kind of crimes do you
usually see around here?
There's some drugs
going through the valley..
..uh, meth, coke
but we deal mostly
with vacationers.
Tourists at the resorts
for spa vacations and such.
[Wayne]
'Could be road rage.'
'Chief gets into a tangle'
there's an accident,
driver's got an attitude, a gun.
- Maybe.
- Not likely.
What are you doing?
I'm checking
the chief's height.
She's about five or six inches
shorter than I am.
The driver's seat is set back
for someone at least my height.
Maybe she was
in the passenger seat.
Passenger air bag didn't go off.
Seat was empty.
So where was she?
[rattling]
Ahh.
[Wayne]
'Blood.'
So she was shot
somewhere else
killer thought she was dead,
put her in the trunk.
But she's alive,
and she opens the escape latch
trunk pops open
killer's startled,
he crashes the car.
She gets out of the trunk
killer shoots her
in the head here.
She's not in a uniform,
so she came from home.
Voila.
You start inside.
I'll look around the property.
[clearing throat]
[door opening]
CBI. Don't move.
Whoa! Take it easy.
On your knees.
Hands on your head.
- No problem.
- Do it now.
[girl #1]
'Leave him alone!'
[man #1]
'Annie, put that down!'
Everybody stay calm.
Damn it,
I told you to stay put!
- Now put that down!
- I mean it. Drop it!
Annie, do what I said!
Listen to him.
[Teresa]
What's the hell's
going on?
- Tommy?
- Teresa?
- Annabeth?
- Annie.
- What are you doing here?
- What're youdoing here?
- Wait, you know these people?
- This is my brother Tommy.
- Hey, how's it going?
- And my niece Annabeth.
Annie. It's Annie.
No one calls me Annabeth.
Put the gun..
Put the gun down.
Put it down.
I swear to god, Rees,
I told her to stay outside.
[theme music]
[Teresa]
You could have killed somebody
or gotten killed.
- Hey, it's a tough business.
- Hey, quit that.
She knows not to touch
the guns in the field.
- In the field?
- Not ever.
Jeez. Sorry for trying
to help out.
[sighing]
She is sorry.
She just won't admit it.
[chuckling]
Who's that remind you of?
What the hell is going on?
Why are you here?
What're you doing?
I'm looking for a skip..
A fugitive,
someone who skipped bail.
I know what a skip is.
Since when are you
a bounty hunter?
I'm a bail enforcement agent.
When I saw you last year
you were building decks
with Eddie Duncan.
Well, nobody wants a deck when
the bank's at the door, Rees.
I took a course in April.
Tig Muldoon, Margo's cousin?
He's a bondsman.
He gave me a shot.
I brought in six guys
in the past two months
made, like, four grand.
Tommy, Tommy..
- Don't even start.
- With what?
Busting my chops
like you always do.
Well, you don't.
I know what I'm doing.
I'm a professional.
Oh, right.
Taking your 13-year-old
daughter along..
that's very professional.
She's 14
and that's not fair, because
I did not want to bring her.
My psycho ex went to Miami
with her boyfriend
so I got her.
[sighing]
You look good.
You...do something
with your hair?
You should be encouraging me.
I'm trying here.
[scoffing]
Okay. What's the name
of your fugitive?
His name's Carmine O'Brien.
Jumped bail out of St. Louis.
I found out about three days ago
he bought a bus ticket here
so I called this Chief Green
and I asked her to keep
an eye out for him.
I heard on my scanner
she got shot.
So you think the chief found
O'Brien and then he killed her?
- Yeah, I don't know, maybe.
- Why break into her house?
Door was open.
I just went in to find out
what I could about O'Brien.
Okay. When we pick him up,
I'll tell you.
If he had any part in this
murder, I can't give him to you.
What if I get to him first?
- Yeah, right.
- You don't think I can do it?
- No, I don't.
- Fine. We'll see.
- Can you watch Annie?
- Are you kidding?
No. No.
This is really dangerous work
I'm doing.
Your office is a lot safer
than my van, right?
'Besides, she needs
some female time.'
Her mom's such a freaking
wackadoo, and you know
I'm a guy.
- Damn it, Tommy.
- Annie!
'You're spending the day
with your Aunt Teresa!'
- 'Come on! Get your bag!'
- Cool.
It is on,sis.
May the best man win.
Oh, man.
Hey.
Carmine O'Brien
is an accountant from St. Louis.
He was arrested three months
ago for embezzlement
'skipped town
right before the trial.'
Spent summers
growing up in Fairmont.
Might explain
why he's hiding here.
Any history of violence?
No. Strictly white collar.
Ivy League-educated,
no prior arrests.
It's hard to see
this guy shooting a cop.
Doesn't mean he didn't do it.
Have Cho go back to Fairmont
and ask around.
Run his credit card
and phone records
have Rigsby
put out a bolo.
Alright.
- OfficerPrice. Hi.
- Hi.
'Can I help you?'
I felt bad about
not checking that trunk.
Should have caught
that, so, uh..
...I went through
the chief's files.
She pulled over a DUI
day before yesterday..
Russian guy
named Dmitri Zubov.
He's staying at one
of the resorts.
What about him
caught your eye?
He blew a .076
on a breathalyzer.
.76? That's under the limit.
He wasn't drunk, but the chief
arrested him anyway
which is a waste of time,
'cause once it goes to court
the judge is just
gonna throw it out.
She was a real stickler
for details.
Thanks.
We'll check it out.
I want to help out
any way I can.
I know the locals
and I can help out
with interviews.
We'll let you know.
Two fingers.
Just dip and remove.
No hesitation.
Want to give it a try?
Okay.
- Did you feel that?
- Well, just slightly.
- You're good.
Picking pockets. Nice.
I promised I'd show her
if she'd tell me
her Aunty Rees stories.
- Don't you dare.
- Of course not.
I was just stringing him along.
You were, were you?
I guess I won't give you this.
- Hey.
- Annabeth?
- Annie.
Annie,Jane and I
have to go to work.
Mind hanging out
in my office?
Sure.
Rigsby's a nice, easy mark
if you want to keep practicing.
The DUI, Zubov?
He's an economist.
He's in Fairmont for
some sort of trade conference.
He stayed on for vacation.
Fascinating, but not what
you really want to talk about.
I cannot believe
my brother's a bounty hunter.
All of a sudden
he's some sort of tough guy?
Who is he fooling?
Not you.
You know what bugs me?
He didn't tell me.
I'd have told him
it's a bad idea.
He just had to
pick up the phone
but instead, nothing.
I basically raised
that punk and his brothers.
It's not my fault
if he doesn't communicate.
[elevator bell dinging]
You think it ismy fault.
No, I didn't say that.
You said that.
I say live and let live.
You'll all be happier.
Oh, mind your own business.
Last name O'Brien,
first name Carmine.
Gonna e-mail you a picture
right now.
Let me know if there's any hits.
Thanks. Bye.
- Hey.
You just called in
a bolo for O'Brien, right?
Yep.
Nice.
[keyboard keys clacking]
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Your Sig Sauer, is that a .357,
a .40, or the 9-millimeter?
It's a 9-millimeter.
Great gun.
Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
Forensics just came back.
No prints off
Chief Green's cruiser.
Killer must have wiped the car.
You got anything
on O'Brien's family in his file?
Uh, his parents are dead.
He's an only child.
If you're looking for leads,
should check the ex-girlfriend.
They have a kid together.
Alright. Thanks.
We'll look into it.
No problem.
- So do you have a girlfriend?
- Yes, I do, as it happens.
- Are you in love with her?
- Oh, good question.
It's hard to say.
I mean..
Is she cute?
You know, maybe you should wait
in your Aunt Teresa's office.
Hey..
[sighing]
[Teresa]
'Mr. Zubov, tell us
about your arrest.'
'I stand charged with a crime
I did not commit.'
Chief Green insisted
I was drunk.
I was not, but she would not
listen to reason.
Did you have any contact with
Chief Green after your arrest?
Can get you something
to drink?
- It's very hot.
- No, thank you, Mr. Zubov.
Just answer the question,
please.
No.
No contact with Chief Green.
'And where were you
last night?'
Last night I had something
to eat, I had a drink.
I had a little more to drink,
but, uh, heh, no driving.
[woman #1]
'Mr. Zubov?'
Are you ready
for your massage?
A new girl. Hello.
Duty calls. Am I done?
Mr. Zubov's gonna
have to reschedule.
Of course.
Now it's all very clear.
You're quite the, uh,
sex fiend, aren't you?
[chuckling]
What do you mean?
Well, you automatically tried
to seduce Agent Lisbon here
but it was the masseuse that
really got your blood pumping.
You're like an owl
watching a mouse.
No. I'm not.
Chief Green thought
you'd committed a crime
but it wasn't drunk driving,
was it? What was it, I wonder?
- This is ridiculous.
- No.
You know what's ridiculous?
Is this. This, uh, ascot..
- Give me this back.
- That's ridiculous. No.
You mind sharing with us
how you got those scratches
on your neck?
I was hiking and boom..
I fell.
[chuckling]
Hiking.
Really?
Yes, hiking.
I refuse to
discuss this further.
Now all we have to do is find
the woman he assaulted.
Well, she's reluctant to make
a public accusation.
That's why, uh, chief hung
the DUI on Zubov.
To buy time to convince
the victim to testify.
It fits.
Butwithout an actual victim,
we don't have anything.
I can't even get
a search warrant for his room.
Zubov's an opportunist.
The question is,
where did he have opportunity?
[knocking]
CBI.
Chad Carmichael,
operations manager here.
What I can I do for you?
We're investigating a crime that
relates to one of your guests
Dmitri Zubov.
Oh. What did he do?
We're not at liberty to say,
but what we're gonna need is
a list of your staff who've
been in Mr. Zubov's room
and security camera
footage
from the hallway
outside his door.
Uh, that's problematic.
Mr. Zubov is a valued guest.
It's cold in here.
Is-is that your, uh,
own personal air conditioner?
Uh, yes.
Fancy. A place like this
doesn't have central air?
I guess I just like it cold.
What's going on here?
[sighing]
Dad.
This is my father,
Philip Carmichael.
- 'He owns the resort.'
- Government people, are you?
These people are with CBI.
They need information
about a guest.
And you didn't call me?
It is myjob.
I'm handling it.
[Philip clearing throat]
We're happy to assist
law enforcement at any time.
We just need a search warrant.
I can't give you the details,
but Mr. Zubov may be involved
in the murder of Chief Green.
This is extremely important.
- Oh, my god. Really?
- And I sympathize.
But we have to respect
the privacy of our guests.
Son, show them out.
And next time, call.
Does the old tyrant always
talk to you like that?
So you're thinking maybe
Zubov killed Chief Green?
Yes, possibly.
I'll get the video for you.
Wait here.
Thank you, chad.
Not easy with a father like
that, but thank you.
Appreciate it.
[door opening]
Mmm.
- 'You still in Fairmont?'
- Yeah.
Go to 787 Elm Street.
O'Brien's there right now.
How'd you get the address?
His ex has been getting calls
from a cell.
We accessed that cell's GPS
and pulled the location.
Got it.
O'Brien!
O'Brien! CBI! Don't move!
Hey!
[car horn honking]
[tires screeching]
[gasping]
[groaning]
Ow!
You okay?
[panting]
It's either a sprained muscle in
your back or a ruptured disc.
They'll tell you
at the hospital.
- I'm fine.
- Go to the hospital!
[cellphone ringing]
- Yeah, okay.
- What's up?
'I've been going through
the security footage'
and I may have found
the woman Zubov assaulted.
It's a maid. She's crying,
and her uniform is torn.
Work schedule says her name
is Sofia Chavez.
Alright. Bring her in.
- How's your guy?
- He's hurt pretty bad.
- Yeah, looked pretty rough.
- You shouldn't have been here.
I told you I was
going after O'Brien.
I mean, stuff happens
when you're chasing guys.
It could have been me
that got knocked.
Your daughter got shot
this morning
I've got a guy
in the hospital
because you don't know
what you're doing.
Oh, like hell, I don't.
You know how I got O'Brien?
He's a Type 1 Diabetic,
and I paid the pharmacist
to tell me when he comes
to buy insulin.
That's skill.
Your people think of that?
Somebody could have
gotten killed.
I love you, but..
"I love you, but.."
But what, sis?
"But...you're a loser. You'll
always be a loser. Just quit."
I love you, but you and Annabeth
need to go home.
Tommy, you should think
about going back to school
learn a trade.
You always liked electronics.
Okay, sure.
Trade school it is.
You want me to detail your car
for you before I go?
Agent Lisbon,
we've set up roadblocks
and we're sending officers
to look for O'Brien.
- 'You want to talk to 'em?'
- We'll finish this later.
I have nothing to say.
I go in room,
I clean, I leave.
Wait.
Zubov didn't assault you?
Didn't hurt you?
No.
Sofia, I don't work
for immigration.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
I promise.
So this is just us?
No police?
No.
Just us.
[sighing]
I clean room.
I think I alone.
He come out of bathroom.
He put hand on me. He..
He rip my, um, this.
- He ripped your uniform.
- Yes.
I scared. I run for door.
He grab me.
I fight.
I get out.
Who told Chief Green
about it?
I told.
She was my friend.
She tell me to accuse Zubov,
but I say no.
She say she keep him
until I change my mind..
...but I no change.
He kill her?
It's a possibility.
That's why it's so important
for you to come forward.
Why?
The rich, they get away
with everything.
[sighing]
Any luck finding O'Brien?
- Look--
- We're leaving tomorrow.
Maybe you're right. Maybe
I'm not cut out for this.
Really?
Yeah, really. What business
do I have bounty hunting?
Truth is, it's not the first
time I thought about quitting.
- Tommy..
- It's probably for the best.
Annabeth will dismember me if we
leave without saying good-bye.
You want to
get lunch tomorrow?
Sure. Yeah.
[door opening]
[man #2]
'This is absurd.'
There is no victim of
an assault. Where is she?
Well, there is a victim.
Sofia Chavez.
Victim? Please.
I ask her to touch me--
- Dmitri..
- It's okay. It's okay.
I ask. She refuses.
That's all.
I only ask her
because my masseuse that day
was little bit ugly, you know?
I see. And normally
you assault your masseuse?
[scoffing]
You make it sound so crude.
I love women.
And love is beautiful, no?
Alright. You have
no case here, agent.
Unless there's
anything else...
Mr. Zubov, we checked
the security footage.
You weren't back
until after 12:00
the night of
Chief Green's murder.
- Where were you?
- You don't have to answer.
We'll find out where you were.
It's just a question of time.
[speaking indistinctly]
I went to Chief Green's home.
- Son of a bitch.
- To discuss my arrest.
To see if something
could be done.
[chuckling]
It's starting to become
a bit tedious here.
You went to bribe her?
I was hoping to find a mutual
acceptable resolution.
But a friend
of the chief's arrives.
A big woman.
Uh, Jori. Jori,
I think her name was.
She was upset.
About what, I don't know.
- And I left.
- Jori?
Must be Jori Kasser.
Uh, the Russian was with
Chief Green when I got there
but he left right away.
What were you doing that late
at the chief's house?
Chief Green
had left a message.
Wanted to know
where my son Steven was.
You know why
she was looking for him?
Steven has
some drug problems.
Knows a bit about
Fairmont's seedy side.
Chief would go to him for
information from time to time.
Chief Green said
that a fugitive
might be hiding out
in Fairmont
and wanted to know if Steven
had heard anything about him.
Why not call?
Why go in person?
I needed to ask a favor.
Um, I'd overheard Steven say
that he was going up
to a cabin in the woods.
'I know what he does there.
He buys drugs.'
And I asked the chief,
if that was what he was doing
to get him
into a treatment program.
He really wants to get clean.
We need to speak to your son.
Where's he?
[sighing]
That's the thing.
I haven't heard from Steven
since I talked to the chief.
Steve's missing?
Why didn't you say
anything?
I was hoping
it was a coincidence.
Sometimes he disappears.
Do you think your son
had something to do
with the murder
of Chief Green?
[voice breaking]
No, not if he was sober.
Hey, boss.
Jori Kasser says her son
might've been involved
in the murder.
Apparently he was buying drugs
up at some cabin.
- Gonna check it out.
- Call my cell if anything.
I'm gonna be out of the office.
- Anything on Zubov?
- Yeah, Van Pelt's on it.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Problem?
M.E. puts the time of death
between 2:00 and 3:00 a.m.
Zubov was in his room
from midnight on.
- He couldn't be the killer.
- Mm.
He was a non-starter anyhow.
And Sofia Chavez
won't testify against him.
We can't even touch
the scumbag.
The world's full of scumbags
we can't touch.
I know, I know.
It's just..
I hear you. It'd soothe
your troubled soul
if you could just stick it
to this particular scumbag.
Well, yeah. I guess
it kind of would.
Shall we?
[car door closing]
They're, uh, rental cabins
for vacationers.
But they're being
renovated now.
Pretty isolated.
Get many drug buys up here?
Heard rumors there were.
Hard to imagine Steve
hanging out in these parts.
He's not what you'd call
a country boy.
That pile of leaves there.
Who's raking leaves up here?
Phew!
[sighing and sniffling]
Steve Kasser?
I better call his mother.
Yeah.
[indistinct conversation]
Mr. Zubov?
Are you ready
for your massage?
Ah, very nice.
Yes, please.
Uh, lead the way.
[cellphone ringing]
Hmm.
[ringing continues]
Rigsby. What's the word?
Lisbon's not answering
her phone.
- Any idea where she is?
- Nope.
We got another vic
dead by a rental cabin.
Maybe connected
to Chief Green.
- Drug thing, looks like.
- Cocaine?
Yeah. Victim had
about five grams on him.
Hmm. Is there just
one cabin
or are others nearby?
There's a few.
[clattering]
[Zubov yelling indistinctly]
[Zubov]
'I-I made a mistake!
I didn't know that..'
Uh, gotta go.
I'll see you up there later.
- 'If I knew..'
- What?
[Van Pelt]
You're under arrest
for solicitation
sexual assault,
assault on a police officer..
Wait, please..
You've the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
[gunshots]
Nice shooting.
I practice a lot
on the gun range with dad.
It's good that you spend time
with your dad
'but you should do other
stuff too. Kid stuff.'
Why? I already know
what I wanna do.
Really? What's that?
I wanna be a cop.
Like you.
I'm flattered. I am.
I don't think you really
know what you want yet.
You don't have to.
It's okay.
- Yeah, I do.
- I sleep five hours a night.
I haven't been able to get away
to see you and your dad
and your uncles in over a year.
That's not what you want.
Aunt Teresa, you get paid
to carry a Glock.
You beat up people
when they get out of line.
- You're totally badass.
- My point still stands.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
You got a text
while you were gone.
- I did?
- Yeah.
- How'd you do?
- I kicked butt.
Yes, she did.
I gotta go back to work.
- Already?
- Yeah.
Keep in touch.
Absolutely, Rees.
I'll call you
when I learn that trade.
- Bye.
[buttons beeping]
Hey, Rigs.
I got your text.
'Did you find Steve Kasser?'
Yeah, he's been dead
a couple days.
'Damn. That's a shame.
Did the coroner show up?'
'Nope. They should be soon.'
[Wayne]
'Those are exit wounds.'
'Steve was shot twice.
Killer used a .380.'
- Same caliber as Chief Green.
- Yeah.
There's more blood over there.
Chief Green's, I'm betting.
So Chief Green comes here
looking for Steve.
Steve's buying coke
from a dealer.
The dealer sees the chief
freaks out and kills
both her and Steve.
He dumps Chief Green
in her police cruiser
and hides Steve here.
Makes sense,
but that scenario
pretty much eliminates
O'Brien as a suspect.
And whatever an Ivy League
accountant was doing in town
he wasn't doing coke.
So he's not the killer.
Why is Philip Carmichael here?
'He owns the cabins.
He's here to let us in.'
Give a yell
if you need anything.
- Okay.
- Have you seen Jane?
Says he'll be up here later.
[unzipping bag]
Will this take long?
It'll take as long
as it takes.
Hey, check it out.
- Someone was staying here.
- Yeah. Recently.
Lot of sugar-free stuff.
O'Brien was a diabetic.
- He could have been here.
- How'd he end up here?
Well, a lot of people knew
these cabins were empty.
Not a bad place
to hide out.
You think he witnessed
the murders?
Maybe.
'Maybe.'
Question is,
where is he now?
But the roadblocks
are still up, right?
Let us know
if you get a hit.
Nothing on O'Brien
from the airport
bus station,
or the train station.
Hey. Welcome back.
[Wayne]
'Doctors say what
the problem is?'
Yeah.
I got hit by a car.
Cho. Good to have you back.
[exhaling]
Thanks.
I got a call from a ranger.
He spotted a man driving down
Black Canyon Fire Road
thirty miles
outside of Fairmont.
'Caucasian, male,
50s, grey hair..'
Sounds like O'Brien.
We're on it.
Uh, Van Pelt, why don't
you go with Rigsby?
Uh, about a mile up ahead
turn right onto the fire road.
Okay.
Lisbon's niece,
sharp girl.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Yeah. Good questions.
- Yeah.
- Do you love her?
What, Annabeth?
- Your girlfriend Sarah.
- Oh, right.
- So?
- I don't see why it matters.
Uh-oh.
Look, we have
a good time together
we enjoy each other's company,
I look forward to seeing her.
Isn't that enough?
Why worry about it?
Trust me,
she's worrying about it.
[sighing]
I just think if you start
talking like that
you're gonna get hurt.
I'm not sure I even know
what that means.
"I love you."
What does that say, really?
I don't know, Wayne.
My last relationship
didn't exactly end well.
I'm probably not the best
person to ask right now.
Fair enough.
There's your right.
[Wayne]
'What the hell!'
[brakes squealing]
Tommy!
Put the gun away, Tommy.
Put the weapon away.
Holster it!
Uh, who are you now?
Hey, what's going on?
O'Brien won't tell us
what he witnessed.
His lawyer won't be here
for a while.
Let him stew. But he's a runner.
Keep him on lockdown.
Okay.
Boss? They just put him
in your office.
I know how you got O'Brien.
The tech guys did
a diagnostic on my phone.
You downloaded spyware
so you could listen
to my conversations.
Sorry.
You couldn't get him yourself,
so you piggybacked on us.
[sighing]
I'm broke, Rees.
Alimony, rent,
friggin' eighth grade prom.
Can you even believe
they have that?
I needed this guy.
So you lied
and cheated your own sister.
I'd really appreciate it
if you give him to me.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I need a favor.
Do you think I'd give you
O'Brien after what you pulled?
Not to mention the fact
that he might be a witness.
Do you even know
how hard this is?
Okay, I am doing you a favor
by not arresting you.
Now go do something
different with your life.
No, you don't tell me
how to live.
Tommy, come on.
I bust my ass every day
to put food on the table
for me and my kid by myself.
Hey, maybe I haven't done
quite as well as you have
but I'm doing
the best that I can
so don't tell me
how to live.
- I'm sorry.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Hello.
[elevator bell dinging]
- Where are we going?
- Uh, Tommy.
- Here's O'Brien, he's yours.
- What?
Go get your bounty.
But you have to leave right now.
Excuse me. I'm very confused.
What is going on?
Annie...pick her up
at the Ellington Inn.
- Isn't she at the motel?
- No, I got her a spa package..
...facial, massage, the works.
She'll be waiting.
- How do you know my daughter?
- Give her my best.
Lisbon.
Are you sure we can't get
O'Brien's public..
- Lisbon.
- ...here any sooner?
No, I..
- What're you doing?
- We've to leave now.
- I need to talk to O'Brien.
- That might be difficult.
- He's not in the building.
- Why not?
Uh, I'll explain to you
on the road.
- I know a great shortcut.
- Where to?
Chad, it's Agent Lisbon
from the CBI.
We need your help.
Yeah, sure, of course.
There's a bounty hunter
on his way to your hotel
to pick up his daughter.
He's traveling with a fugitive.
Wait, that guy
squatting in our cabin?
- My dad was just mentioning--
- Listen..
...tell your father
to get security.
Detain him. We'll be there
in 20 minutes.
[inhaling sharply]
Well, that was
very well played.
- Where is he?
- Give it a minute.
[Patrick]
'Ah-ha! There he is.'
If anything happens to him..
'Everyone's safe,
so don't worry.'
It's all gonna turn out fine.
Shall we?
- You're the bounty hunter.
- Excuse me?
This is about your bounty.
[under breath]
Oh, man.
Hey, I don't have time.
Listen, I just need you
to take O'Brien to Mexico
and let him loose.
You do that, I'll double
whatever they're paying you.
- What?
- Exactly what I said.
- I'll double your bounty.
- I don't do that.
Fine, I'll triple it.
Why?
Look, it doesn't matter.
Will you do it?
You killed Chief Green
and the druggie, didn't you?
You're worried O'Brien
can identify you.
Just...just name your price.
A million bucks.
- Come on. That's not even..
- Whoa!
Might need your daddy's
checkbook for that.
Why? What's going on?
O'Brien didn't witness anything.
He was nowhere near the cabin.
But you were, weren't you?
No. I..
Why would you say that?
Well, you gave us that
videotape so easily.
Practically handed us
Zubov as a suspect
'and then there's the drugs.'
A little partial to the cocaine,
aren't you, Chad?
- No, I'm not.
- Okay, a lot partial.
Dilated pupils, hyper-alert.
You're burning up.
That's why you have this, uh,
personal air conditioner
in an already-cool room.
'And when I shook your hand'
your pulse was thumping
like a jackhammer, my friend.
Okay. Stay there!
Chad, let him go.
Stay there!
Don't be stupid, Chad.
Let him go.
Stay back, I'll shoot him!
I swear I'll shoot him!
[alarm bell ringing]
[both grunting]
Nicely done, Lisbon family.
[bell continues ringing]
Our attorney
will be here soon.
- What's the point?
- Son--
I just wanna
be done with it.
When did you start
dealing drugs?
A year ago.
Look, he doesn't
pay me anything.
Dealing does.
You were dealing to Steve Kasser
the night of the murders?
What happened next?
[Chad]
'That's when the cop came by.'
She told us to take it easy.
Then she started to talk
to Steve about his mother.
'All I could think about was how
my father was gonna disown me'
'how I'm gonna lose everything.'
'I was so high.'
I put Chief Green
in her trunk.
'I tried to get Steven too'
but he was too heavy,
so I left him there.
Look, I didn't wanna
kill Steve, okay?
I didn't wanna kill anybody,
but I had to.
That has to count
for something, right?
No.
[knocking]
- Hey.
The kid wanted to say good-bye.
[chuckling]
Give me a minute
with your aunt, huh?
- Yeah.
- Love you.
Love you too.
Listen, do you still
want O'Brien?
Well...yeah, sure.
He's downstairs in holding.
I'll have them
release him to you.
Wow. Thanks.
This doesn't mean I think
what you're doing is right
but I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
You got a great kid there
so you're obviously
doing something right.
I'm proud of you, Tommy.
Maybe even a little envious.
Thanks, Rees.
I love you, Tommy.
And, um, you know that
I'm always here for you, right?
Yeah, I know that.
Okay.
[exhaling deeply]
[whispering]
Be careful, Tommy.
[theme music]